<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Spekter AIGS</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_initiatives_home">InitiativesHome</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="aigs_tech_exhibition_organised_by_the_bca_department_click_this_tab_to_know_more">T

</string>
    <string name="asc">c</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scanner_project_info">ScannerProjectInfo</string>
    <string name="dummy">Hosting a blockchain code on to a cloud network in order to create a prototype app in the Healthcare sector. Problem Statement short description in a short paragraph Who we are - A young start-up in the Health Tech space. What we plan to achieve – Create a blockchain application to store and share patient records with Doctors and Health care intermediaries. Where we are currently – The team has built the code and UI/UX designs for the application, but we need help to host the program on a network and create a prototype. What we need – We need young professionals to help solve the hosting issue and build the prototype. White Hour Solutions (WHS) LLP., is a young start-up looking to provide a solution for patient to record, store and share their Personal Health Records (PHRs). The PHRs would be interoperable between the patient and other Healthcare intermediaries. We plan to do this by providing an application which can be used through mobile phones, computers or tablets. We are currently at the phase where we have the codes developed and the designs for the app, but need help with hosting it on the cloud and building the prototype. All support and assistance will be provided for the same.</string>
</resources>